Finding Aid for Michel Oksenberg papers
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Academic and Professional Files (mainly correspondence)
  - 1967-1977
    - Rand Corporation, Santa Monica, California, 1968-1972 (Box 9)
    - Reynolds, Bruce (economics professor, Union College, Schenectady, NY), 1975-1976 (Box 9)
    - Ridley, Charles (professor of anthropology at Stanford University), 1970-1972 (Box 9)
    - Research Institute on International Change (RIIC), Columbia University, New York, 1974-1976 (Box 9)
    - Robinson, Thomas (political science professor, University of Washington, Seattle, Washington), 1972-1977 (Box 9)
    - Rockefeller, David (director of the Chase Manhattan Bank and the founder of the Rockefeller Foundation), 1973-1975 (Box 9)
    - Rockefeller Commission on Critical Choices for Americans (Box 9)
    - Correspondence and paper on China by Michel Oksenberg, 1973-1975 (Box 9)
    - Rockefeller University, 1976 (Box 9)
    - Roundtable, National Committee on U.S.-China Relations, 1971 (Box 9)
    - S (miscellaneous), 1967-1977 (Box 9)
    - Sage Publications, Beverly Hills, California, concerning Oksenberg publication, 1976 (Box 9)
    - Scalapino, Robert (political science professor, University of California, Berkeley), 1968-1977 (Box 9)
    - Scholarly Network on Elites and Political Decision making of the Social Science History Association, 1976 (Box 9)
    - School of International Affairs (see SIA) (Box 9)
    - Schroeder Banking Corporation, New York, New York, 1972-1973 (Box 9)
    - Science (periodical of the American Association for the Advancement of Science, Washington, D.C.) concerning book review by Oksenberg, 1975 (Box 9)
    - Seminar on Modern East Asia: China; at Columbia University, 1970-1973 (Box 9)
    - Seminar on the State, concerning China; held at Columbia University, 1968-1970 (Box 9)
    - SIA (School of International Affairs) Tripartite Committee at Columbia University, 1970-1972 (Box 9)
    - Silin, Robert (research proposal on different perceptions of the organization of bureaucratic institutions in the U.S. and abroad), undated (Box 9)
    - Sino-American Conferences
      - 4th Annual meeting, Warrenton, VA., December 1974 (Box 9)
      - 5th Annual meeting, Taipei, China, June, 1975 (Box 9)
    - Sino-American Relations Committee (graduate student group at Columbia University), 1968-1969 (Box 9)
    - Skinner, G. William (anthropology professor at Stanford University, Stanford, California), 1969-1973 (Box 9)
    - Social Science History Association at the University of Pennsylvania, 1976 (Box 9)
    - Social Science Research Council, New York, New York
      - General file, 1971-1977 (Box 9)
      - Annual report, 1973-1974 (Box 9)
      - Barclay Conference in New York City, concerning funding and development of Chinese Studies (see also Conferences--Priorities...; also Barclay Conference), October 1973 (Box 9)
      - Bureaucracy (correspondence concerning meetings and conferences of the group), 1972-1973 (Box 9)
      - Conference on Contemporary China, 1964 (Box 9)
      - Greystone Conference (concerning travel payment of a visiting scholar), 1974 (Box 9)
    - Solomon, Richard (senior staff member, National Security Council), 1969-1977 (Box 9)
    - Sorich, Richard (professor at the East Asian Institute of Columbia University), 1971-1975 (Box 9)
    - Stanford University
      - Local systems for codification of China areas and subjects, 1969 (Box 9)
    - Stanford University Press
      - Recommendations for publishing, 1968-1975 (Box 9)
    - State Department
      - U.S. correspondence 1975-1976 includes paper by Oksenberg, "Planning for the Ford Trip" on the president's visit to China, written in 1975 (Box 9)
    - State Department Conference, 1972 (Box 10)
    - Stavis, Benedict (social scientist from Cornell University, Ithaca, N.Y.), 1969-1977 (Box 10)
    - Stetson University, Deland, Florida, 1969-1972 (Box 10)
    - "Studies and Documents" (Graduate Institute of International Studies periodical)
      - Information concerning periodical (Box 10)
    - Studies in Comparative Communism, UCLA
      - 1974-1975 (Box 10)
        (see also Conferences)
    - Su, M.H., Retires, undated (Box 10)
    - T (miscellaneous), 1968-1977 (Box 10)
    - Taiwan
      - General correspondence, 1965-1973 (Box 10)
      - China conference on Sino-American Relations, held at the Institute of International Relations in Taipei, 1970 (Box 10)
    - Teiwes, Fred (political science professor at Cornell University in Ithaca, N.Y.; later at the Australian National University at Canberra, and the University of Sydney in Australia), 1968-1977 (Box 10)
    - Thomson, James (secretary of Council on Foreign Relations discussion group, U.S. Policy Toward East Asia), 1970 (Box 10)
    - Twentieth Century Fund (non-profit research foundation)
      - Annual report, newsletters, and proposals of others on projects (Box 10)
    - U (miscellaneous), 1969-1977 (Box 10)
    - Understanding China Newsletter, Advisory Board, 1974 (Box 10)
    - United Airlines, concerning missing baggage, 1972 (Box 10)
    - U.S. Civil Service Commission, seminars on International Affairs and Federal Operations, 1969-1971 (Box 10)
    - U.S.-China People's Friendship Association, New York, New York, 1974 (Box 10)
    - Universities Service Centre, Hong Kong
      - Financial reports and correspondence, 1972-1977 (Box 10)
    - University of California Press (re. article reviews), 1975-1977 (Box 10)
    - V (miscellaneous), 1967-1977 (Box 10)
    - Verba, Sidney
      - Statement and reply on U.S. policy toward East Asia, 1968 (Box 10)
    - W (miscellaneous), 1967-1977; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Ward, Robert (director of the Center for Research in International Studies at Stanford University) concerning submission of multi-authored volumes for publication by Prentiss-Hall, 1967-1977 (Box 10)
    - Water Conservancy Technicians in China
      - Reports and lists, 1972 (Box 10)
    - Wegman, Myron E. (dean of the School of Public Health at the University of Michigan) concerning seminar on international health, 1974 (Box 10)
    - Wei, Yung (deputy director of the Institute of International Relations, Taipei, Taiwan), 1976-1977 (Box 10)
    - West View Press (Boulder, Colorado, periodical)
      - Correspondence with Frederick Praeger, president and editorial director concerning Oksenberg's new position and articles on China, 1977 (Box 10)
    - White, Lynn T. (assistant professor of political science at Princeton University in New Jersey), 1976-1977 (Box 10)
    - Whitson, William (colonel working under the Secretary of Defense and later for the Rand Corporation), 1969-1972 (Box 10)
    - Wilbur, Marty (Oksenberg's colleague, formerly his teacher and thesis advisor at Columbia), 1975-1976 (Box 10)
    - Whiting, Allen (political science professor, University of Michigan), 1969-1977 (Box 11)
    - Wingspread (conference center of the Johnson Foundation in Racine, Wisconsin)
      - Correspondence concerning conference, May 1974 (Box 11)
      - Notes and reports from conference (Box 11)
      - Report from conference: "Education" (Box 11)
    - Wirth, Timothy (U.S. congressman from Colorado)
      - Correspondence concerning possible discussion of American policy toward Asia, 1975 (Box 11)
    - Working Group on Republican China, Joint Committee on Contemporary China, Social Science Research Council
      - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 11)
    - X (miscellaneous), 1976 (Box 11)
    - Y (miscellaneous), 1967-1976 (Box 11)
    - Yen Ming (newspaper woman from Hong Kong) concerning visit to U.S., 1973 (Box 11)
    - Yeung, Sai-Cheong (research investigator for the Universities Service Centre, Kowloon, Hong Kong), 1973-1977 (Box 11)
    - Z (miscellaneous), 1968-1977 (Box 11)
    - Miscellaneous materials, 1975-1976
      - Henry Luce Foundation, notebook concerning Luce Scholars Selection Committee meeting of in Atlanta, Georgia, March 18-19, 1976 (Box 11)
      - Social Science Research Council, applications for grants, 1975; 4 folders (Box 11)
  - 1971-1994
    (Chronological File)
    - 1971-1975 (Box 17)
    - 1976 (Box 17)
    - 1977, 8 folders (Box 17)
    - 1978, 9 folders (Box 17)
    - 1979 (Box 17)
    - 1979, 11 folders (Box 18)
    - 1980, 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Miscellaneous notes, 1968-1977 (Box 18)
    - 1980-1990 (Box 47)
    - 1991-1994 (Box 48)
  - 1977-1991
    (People file)
    - Ahn Byung-joon, 1977-1989 (Box 18)
    - Albright, Madeleine, 1983-1989 (Box 18)
    - Andors, Stephen, 1979-1986 (Box 18)
    - Armacost, Michael, 1980-1989 (Box 18)
    - Askew, Reubin, 1982-1983 (Box 18)
    - Bachman, David, 1984-1991 (Box 18)
    - Bailey, J. Albert, 1985-1990 (Box 18)
    - Barnett, A. Doak, 1980-1990; 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Baron, Michael L., 1982-1983 (Box 18)
    - Baum, Richard, 1976-1989 (Box 18)
    - Bernstein, Tom, 1977-1990 (Box 18)
    - Bloomgarden, Kathy, 1980-1983 (Box 18)
    - Blumenthal, W. Michael, 1985-1991 (Box 18)
    - Brademas, John, 1985-1989 (Box 18)
    - Bradshaw, James, 1986 (Box 18)
    - Brown, Cheryl, 1984-1989 (Box 18)
    - Brzezinski, Zbigniew, 1983-1990 (Box 18)
    - Bullock, Mary Brown, 1982-1991 (Box 18)
    - Bundy, McGeorge, 1991 (Box 18)
    - Burns, John P., 1977-1987 (Box 18)
    - Burstein, Andrew M., 1980-1984 (Box 18)
    - Bush, George, 1989 (Box 18)
    - Bush, Richard, 1980-1990 (Box 18)
    - Butler, Steven, 1981-1989 (Box 18)
    - Caldwell, James T., 1981-1987 (Box 19)
    - Carter, Jimmy, 1981-1991 (Box 19)
    - Chamberlain, H.B., 1980-1984 (Box 19)
    - Chang, Parris, 1982-1991 (Box 19)
    - Chi'en, Frederick, 1987-1990 (Box 19)
    - Chimes, Jeanne, 1985 (Box 19)
    - Ching, Frank, 1982-1985 (Box 19)
    - Clarenbach, David, 1990 (Box 19)
    - Personal, alphabetical, cont. (Box 19)
    - Cohen, Jerome A., 1980-1985 (Box 19)
    - Cohen, Paul, 1984 (Box 19)
    - Cohen, Warren, 1980-1991 (Box 19)
    - Cumings, Bruce, 1981-1989 (Box 19)
    - Dai Shen-yu, 1985 (Box 19)
    - Davis, Richard, 1989 (Box 19)
    - DeAngelis, Alexander P., 1982 (Box 19)
    - Dittmer, Lowell, 1977-1989 (Box 19)
    - Dolphin, John, 1980-1988 (Box 19)
    - Donnithorne, Audrey, 1980-1982 (Box 19)
    - Duara, Prasenjit, 1988 (Box 19)
    - Dull, Jack, 1985 (Box 19)
    - Edwards, Randle R., 1982-1988 (Box 19)
    - Elman, Benjamin, 1985-1987 (Box 19)
    - Eno, Robert, 1983-1991 (Box 19)
    - Fairbank, John K., 1977-1991 (Box 19)
    - Falkenheim, Victor, 1980-1984 (Box 19)
    - Fan Tining, 1988 (Box 19)
    - Fang Qiang, 1990 (Box 19)
    - Feng Yushu, 1988 (Box 19)
    - Fenwick, Ann, 1985-1986 (Box 19)
    - Ferraro, Geraldine, 1985 (Box 19)
    - Fischer, William A., 1981-1983 (Box 19)
    - Fisher, Richard, 1986-1987 (Box 19)
    - Fisher, Steve, 1989 (Box 19)
    - Francis, Corinna-Barbara, 1988-1991 (Box 19)
    - Freeman, Charles W., Jr., 1982-1984 (Box 19)
    - Friedman, Edward, 1980-1990 (Box 19)
    - Frolic, Bernard, 1980-1984 (Box 19)
    - Gaenslen, Fritz, 1983-1988 (Box 19)
    - Galloway, Jim, 1989 (Box 19)
    - Garver, John, 1986-1991 (Box 19)
    - Gates, Robert, 1989-1991 (Box 19)
    - Goldman, Merle, 1977-1989 (Box 19)
    - Goldstein, Steven, 1977-1991 (Box 19)
    - Gordon, Richard, 1991 (Box 19)
    - Graham, Billy, 1989 (Box 19)
    - Gries, David D., 1981-1986 (Box 19)
    - Gu Ning, 1985 (Box 19)
    - Han Xu (PRC Ambassador), 1986-1989 (Box 19)
    - Harding, Harry, 1980-1989 (Box 19)
    - Harrison, Selig S., 1977-1990 (Box 19)
    - Hazard, Barbara, 1981-1990 (Box 19)
    - Hearst, Nancy, 1986-1988 (Box 19)
    - Henderson, Gail, 1980-1990 (Box 19)
    - Hoffman, Fred, 1981-1984 (Box 19)
    - Houn, Franklin W., 1980-1983 (Box 19)
    - House, Karen, 1984-1989 (Box 19)
    - Hsieh, Winston, 1989 (Box 19)
    - Hsueh Chun-tu (Box 19)
    - Hu Hua, 1987 (Box 19)
    - Hu Qiaomu, 1989-1991 (Box 19)
    - Hua Logeng, 1984 (Box 19)
    - Huan Guo-cang, 1984-1990 (Box 19)
    - Huang Fanzhang, 1987-1989 (Box 19)
    - Huang, Phil, 1985-1989 (Box 19)
    - Huang, Ray, 1983-1987 (Box 19)
    - Huang Xiaoming, 1987 (Box 19)
    - Huberman, Benjamin, 1981-1986 (Box 19)
    - Huntington, Samuel P., 1980-1984 (Box 19)
    - Ikei, Masaru, 1980-1991 (Box 19)
    - Imai, Hiroyuki, 1985-1986 (Box 19)
    - Ishikawa, Shigeru, 1987 (Box 19)
    - Javeline, Debbie, 1989 (Box 19)
    - Ji Xiaolin, 1987-1989 (Box 19)
    - Joffe, Ellis, 1980-1989 (Box 19)
    - Jones, Eric, 1987-1991 (Box 19)
    - Judd, Walter H., 1985 (Box 19)
    - Kallgren, Joyce, 1979-1990 (Box 19)
    - Kau Ying-mao, 1977-1991 (Box 19)
    - Keightley, David N., 1981-1987 (Box 19)
    - Kennedy, Edward M., 1980-1991 (Box 19)
    - Kent, Ann, 1980-1990 (Box 19)
    - Kirkpatrick, Jeane, 1988 (Box 19)
    - Kissinger, Henry, 1987-1991 (Box 19)
    - Kokubun, Ryosei, 1983-1986 (Box 19)
    - Kramer, Michael, 1989-1990 (Box 19)
    - Kraus, Richard, 1980-1992 (Box 19)
    - Lampton, D. Michael, 1980-1987 (Box 19)
    - Lardy, Nicholas, 1977-1991 (Box 19)
    - Laux, David N., 1983-1987 (Box 20)
    - Lawson, Eugene, 1973-1989 (Box 20)
    - Lee Hong Yung, 1977-1989 (Box 20)
    - Levin, Herbert, 1985-1986 (Box 20)
    - Lewis, John W., 1980-1991 (Box 20)
    - Li Bozhong, 1991 (Box 20)
    - Li Fan, 1985 (Box 20)
    - Li Jian-jun, 1980-1981 (Box 20)
    - Li Rui, circa 1989 (Box 20)
    - Li Yi-chun, 1986 (Box 20)
    - Li Zehou, 1991 (Box 20)
    - Liao, K.S. (Tony), 1984-1989 (Box 20)
    - Lilley, James, 1981-1989 (Box 20)
    - Lin Han-sheng, 1989 (Box 20)
    - Lin Zhimin, 1987-1989 (Box 20)
    - Link, Perry, 1984-1988 (Box 20)
    - Lintner, Bertil, 1987-1988 (Box 20)
    - Liu Guoguang, 1987-1988 (Box 20)
    - Liu Kinming, 1990 (Box 20)
    - Liu, Paul, 1980-1985 (Box 20)
    - Liu Yia-ling, 1989 (Box 20)
    - Lord, Winston, 1986-1991 (Box 20)
    - Ma, Stephen, 1986-1989 (Box 20)
    - Maccoby, Eleanor E., 1981 (Box 20)
    - MacFarquhar, Roderick, 1979-1991 (Box 20)
    - Maddox, Pat, 1977-1990 (Box 20)
    - Madsen, Richard, 1987-1988 (Box 20)
    - Madsen, Robert, Jr., 1988-1990 (Box 20)
    - Maier, John, 1980-1988 (Box 20)
    - Manion, Melanie, 1989-1991 (Box 20)
    - Marks, Robert, 1985 (Box 20)
    - Martin, Robin, 1981-1987 (Box 20)
    - McCormick, Barrett, 1989-1990 (Box 20)
    - McWilliams, James P., 1980 (Box 20)
    - Mitchell, Henry, 1985-1987 (Box 20)
    - Mondale, Walter F., 1981-1991 (Box 20)
    - Moody, Peter, 1980-1988 (Box 20)
    - Moore, Jeanne, 1985-1991 (Box 20)
    - Moriyama, Akio, 1988-1989 (Box 20)
    - Mosher, Steven, 1981-1987 (Box 20)
    - Moyer, Charles, 1982 (Box 20)
    - Murray, Doug, 1979-1991 (Box 20)
    - Myers, James T., 1977-1984 (Box 20)
    - Naquin, Susan, 1987-1988 (Box 20)
    - Nathan, Andrew J., 1980-1989 (Box 20)
    - Naughton, Barry, 1987-1991 (Box 20)
    - Nealer, Kevin, 1983 (Box 20)
    - Nelsen, Harvey, 1980-1984 (Box 20)
    - Neuhauser, Charles, 1981-1989 (Box 20)
    - Newby, Laura J., 1989 (Box 20)
    - Nixon, Richard M., 1982-1990 (Box 20)
    - Odom, William, 1982-1985 (Box 20)
    - Ogata, Sadako, 1982-1990 (Box 20)
    - Ogden, Suzanne, 1980-1982 (Box 20)
    - Olembert, Thola, 1986 (Box 20)
    - Paine, Lynn, 1986-1991 (Box 20)
    - Pan, Loretta, 1982-1987 (Box 20)
    - Parish, William L., 1981-1984 (Box 20)
    - Pastor, Robert, 1982-1987 (Box 20)
    - Parker, Maynard, 1980-1989 (Box 20)
    - Peng Di, 1990-1992 (Box 20)
    - Pepper, Suzanne, 1981-1984 (Box 20)
    - Perkins, Dwight H., 1980-1987 (Box 20)
    - Perry, Elizabeth, 1977-1990 (Box 20)
    - Pollack, Jonathan, 1980-1983 (Box 20)
    - Power, Eugene B., 1982-1988 (Box 20)
    - Power, Philip and Sarah, 1980-1990 (Box 20)
    - Prewitt, Kenneth, 1980-1984 (Box 20)
    - Pusey, Nathan, 1981-1983 (Box 20)
    - Pye, Lucian, 1980-1990 (Box 20)
    - Pyle, Kenneth B., 1980-1990 (Box 20)
    - Raddock, David, 1979-1987 (Box 20)
    - Rawski, Evelyn, 1981-1985 (Box 20)
    - Rawski, Thomas, 1980-1991 (Box 20)
    - Ray, Dennis M., 1986-1990 (Box 20)
    - Reardon-Anderson, James, 1980-1987 (Box 20)
    - Rehmus, Charles, 1983 (Box 20)
    - Reynolds, Bruce, 1977-1987 (Box 20)
    - Ridley, Charles, 1987-1989 (Box 20)
    - Rittenberg, Sidney, 1982 (Box 20)
    - Robinson, Thomas W., 1980-1988 (Box 20)
    - Rorty, Amelie Oksenberg, 1980-1990 (Box 20)
    - Rosen, Stanley, 1977-1986 (Box 20)
    - Rosenau, James N., 1985-1987 (Box 20)
    - Ross, Lester, 1977-1988 (Box 21)
    - Ross, Robert, 1985-1991; 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Ruan Ming, 1989-1991 (Box 21)
    - Rustow, Dankwart, 1989-1990 (Box 21)
    - Saich, Tony, 1989-1990 (Box 21)
    - Sands, Lee, 1986-1989 (Box 21)
    - Scalapino, Robert A., 1979-1989 (Box 21)
    - Schell, Orville, 1984-1991 (Box 21)
    - Schnepp, Otto, 1982-1985 (Box 21)
    - Schram, Stuart R., 1982-1984 (Box 21)
    - Scowcroft, Brent, 1988-1991 (Box 21)
    - Schwarcz, Vera, 1985-1989 (Box 21)
    - Seldon, Mervyn, 1980-1981 (Box 21)
    - Shirk, Susan, 1980-1991 (Box 21)
    - Shue, Vivienne, 1980-1990 (Box 21)
    - Simon, Denis Fred, 1980-1987 (Box 21)
    - Skinner, G. William, 1981-1991 (Box 21)
    - Slawecki, Leon, 1985 (Box 21)
    - Solarz, Stephen J., 1981-1987 (Box 21)
    - Solin, Gail, 1988 (Box 21)
    - Solinger, Dorothy, 1980-1991 (Box 21)
    - Solomon, Richard H., 1979-1991 (Box 21)
    - Spence, Jonathan, 1982-1989 (Box 21)
    - Stahl, Leslie, 1989 (Box 21)
    - Stampfer, Joshua, 1983-1984 (Box 21)
    - Starr, John Bryan, 1980-1981 (Box 21)
    - Stavis, Benedict, 1977-1991 (Box 21)
    - Stiefbold, Annette, 1987 (Box 21)
    - Stolper, Thomas, 1984-1989 (Box 21)
    - Suleski, Ronald, 1977-1991 (Box 21)
    - Sullivan, Lawrence, 1978-1991 (Box 21)
    - Suttmeier, Richard (Pete), 1980-1989 (Box 21)
    - Terrill, Ross, 1980-1985 (Box 21)
    - Teiwes, F.C., 1978-1987 (Box 21)
    - Thaxton, Ralph, 1980-1988 (Box 21)
    - Thurston, Anne, 1986 (Box 21)
    - Tow, William T., 1980-1989 (Box 21)
    - Tsao, King K., 1989 (Box 21)
    - Tsou Tang, 1980-1990; 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Van Ness, Peter, 1983-1988 (Box 21)
    - Wakeman, Carolyn, 1985-1989 (Box 21)
    - Wakeman, Frederic, 1980-1991 (Box 21)
    - Walder, Andrew, 1984-1989 (Box 21)
    - Wang, Jimmie, 1983-1989 (Box 21)
    - Wang Ming-phou, 1986-1987 (Box 21)
    - Wang, Vincent Wei-cheng, 1987-1989 (Box 21)
    - Wang Zhidong, 1989-1990 (Box 21)
    - Wei Yung, 1988-1989 (Box 21)
    - Whiting, Allen, 1981-1990 (Box 21)
    - Whyte, Lynn, 1987-1991 (Box 21)
    - Wilhelm, Alfred, 1987-1991 (Box 21)
    - Wilson, David, 1987-1990 (Box 21)
    - Wilson, Richard W., 1977-1987 (Box 21)
    - Winkler, Edwin A., 1971-1975 (Box 21)
    - Winkelman, Stanley J., 1977-1978 (Box 21)
    - Wirth, Timothy E., 1979-1989 (Box 22)
    - Wong, Francisco, 1989 (Box 22)
    - Wong, R. Bin, 1981-1988 (Box 22)
    - Woodard, Kim, 1986-1990 (Box 22)
    - Woodruff, John, 1982-1991; 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Yahuda, Michael, 1986-1990 (Box 22)
    - Yan Jiaqi, 1988 (Box 22)
    - Yang, Ben, 1986 (Box 22)
    - Yee, Albert, 1983 (Box 22)
    - Yu Bin, 1985-1991 (Box 22)
    - Yu Xiaoping, 1991 (Box 22)
    - Zagoria, Don, 1977-1984 (Box 22)
    - Zeidman, Philip F., 1982-1990 (Box 22)
    - Zhao Baoxu, 1982-1988 (Box 22)
    - Zhao Fusan, 1985-1991 (Box 22)
    - Zhi Bingchen, 1987-1988 (Box 22)
    - Miscellaneous A-Z, 1984-1991; 2 folders (Box 22)
  - 1977-1991
    (Organizations file)
    - Academy for Educational Development, 1987 (Box 22)
    - Alberta Economic Development, 1985-1986 (Box 22)
    - All Star Teachers, 1990 (Box 22)
    - American Agenda, 1988 (Box 22)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Slavic Studies, 1986 (Box 22)
    - American Civil Liberties Union (Morison case), 1986 (Box 22)
    - American Consul Hong Kong, 1983 (Box 22)
    - American Political Science Association, 1984-1991 (Box 22)
    - Ann Arbor News, 1983-1986 (Box 22)
    - ARCO Gas and Oil Company, 1991 (Box 22)
    - Asia Foundation, 1985-1991 (Box 22)
    - The Asia Society, 1990-1991 (Box 22)
    - The Asian Survey, 1982-1991 (Box 22)
    - The Atlantic Council, 1984-1987 (Box 22)
    - BBC (British Broadcasting Corp.), 1990 (Box 22)
    - Banca Nationale Dell'Agricoltura, 1981-1983 (Box 22)
    - Bechtel, 1984-1986 (Box 22)
    - Beijing Review, 1988 (Box 22)
    - Boeing China, 1989-1991 (Box 22)
    - Book Review Requests/ Book Reviews, 1981-1988 (Box 22)
    - BP America, 1988-1989 (Box 22)
    - The Brookings Institution, 1977-1985 (Box 22)
    - The Burroughs Corporation, 1981-1985 (Box 22)
    - Cambridge University Press, 1981-1987 (Box 22)
    - Center for National Policy, 1981-1990 (Box 22)
    - Central Intelligence Agency, 1977-1991 (Box 22)
    - Chase-Manhattan Bank, 1980-1989 (Box 22)
    - China Institute in America, Inc., 1981-1990 (Box 22)
    - China-PRC Ambassadors, 1980-1985 (Box 22)
    - China-PRC Embassy, 1983-1989 (Box 22)
    - China Quarterly, 1989-1991 (Box 22)
    - China Round Table, 1982-1983 (Box 22)
    - China Symposium '89, 1988-1989 (Box 22)
    - China Times, 1988 (Box 22)
    - Chinese Embassy, Washington, DC, 1990-1991 (Box 22)
    - Chinese Scholars of Political Science and International Relations, 1988 (Box 22)
    - Columbia University Chinese Studies, 1979-1991 (Box 22)
    - Committee on Foreign Relations (US Senate), 1987 (Box 22)
    - Committee on International Relations Studies with the PRC, 1988-1991; 2 folders (Box 23)
    - Comparative Politics (journal), 1985-1987 (Box 23)
    - Comparative Politics Conference, 1988 (Box 23)
    - Congressional Research Service, 1990-1991 (Box 23)
    - Coordination Council for North American Affairs, 1987-1991 (Box 23)
    - Cornell University Press, 1991 (Box 23)
    - Corning Glass, 1984-1988 (Box 23)
    - Country Music Association, 1987 (Box 23)
    - Crank Letters, 1989 (Box 23)
    - The Ditchley Foundation, 1980-1989 (Box 23)
    - East-West Center, 1990-1991; 2 folders (Box 23)
    - Economic Dinner Group, 1982-1991 (Box 23)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1980-1982 (Box 23)
    - ESSO Eastern, Inc., 1982-1985 (Box 23)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1982 (Box 23)
    - The Florida Economics Club, 1989 (Box 23)
    - The Ford Foundation, 1980-1989 (Box 23)
    - Foreign Affairs (journal), 1985-1991 (Box 23)
    - Foreign Relations of the US (FRUS) Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 23)
    - Foundation for Books to China, 1988 (Box 23)
    - Four Anniversaries China Conference, 1988-1989 (Box 23)
    - General Foods World Food Prize, 1989 (Box 23)
    - Gilbert Festschrift, 1989 (Box 23)
    - Governor's Commission on China, 1985-1986 (Box 23)
    - Harvard International Review, 1988-1991 (Box 23)
    - Harvard University, 1981-1985 (Box 23)
    - The Henry M. Jackson Foundation, 1984-1985 (Box 23)
    - Institute of American Culture (Taiwan), 1989 (Box 23)
    - Institute of International Relations (Taiwan), 1985-1992 (Box 23)
    - International Communication Agency, 1978-1984 (Box 23)
    - Japan Broadcasting Corporation, 1991 (Box 23)
    - Kissinger Associates (America-China Society), 1989-1991 (Box 23)
    - Koppel Communications, 1989 (Box 23)
    - Korea, 1986-1988 (Box 23)
    - Kramer Associates, Inc., 1986 (Box 23)
    - The Learning Channel, 1989 (Box 23)
    - Lectures, 1989 (Box 23)
    - The Luce Foundation, 1989-1991 (Box 23)
    - The MacArthur Foundation, 1990-1991 (Box 23)
    - MacNeil-Lehrer Newshour, 1984-1991 (Box 23)
    - Michigan China Council, 1986-1991 (Box 23)
    - Mobil Oil, 1980-1982 (Box 23)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1980-1987 (Box 23)
    - National Committee on US-China Relations (NCUSCR), 1989-1990
      - Agendas and Memoranda, 1985 (Box 23)
      - Memoranda, 1988-1991 (Box 24)
      - US-China Relations Dialogue, 1985-1987; 2 folders (Box 24)
    - National Conference of Editorial Writers (NCEW), 1987 (Box 24)
    - The National Council for US-China Trade, 1982-1988 (Box 24)